Brendon O'Neill

24 Millennium Court,

Hebron road,

Kilkenny.

Brendonpjon@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Portfolio</u>

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated and hardworking front-end developer with five years' experience as a graphic designer. I'm passionate to learn new skills or to undertake new challenges to improve my current skillset. I am able to work independently or within a team setting in busy environments.

Technical Skills

Development skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, React, Node JS, Express JS, Mongo DB, Python, Kotlin, NPM, GIT.

Design skills: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere Pro, Affinity

Designer/Photo, Canvas, Gimp, Figma.

Education

Bachelor of Science (Honours) Creative Computing

Waterford Institute of Technology 2019 - 2020 1st Class Honours

Bachelor of Science Multimedia Applications Development

Waterford Institute of Technology 2016 - 2019 Pass with Merit, Grade 1

QQI Level 5 Multimedia

Waterford College of Further Education 2015 - 2016
Distinction

Work Experience

Veri - Software for Digital Training Programme Management

Multimedia Specialist, Marketing Team.

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

- I was tasked to create daily social media post to advertise the products of Veri.
- I designed the web page to select an application from Veri's website.
- Performed user experience tests on different builds of the applications / developed video guides on how to use the applications.
- Worked with the marketing team analysing the best methods that attract traffic to the website and different method of advertising the products.

Millennium Court Community After Schools Service

Website developer.

Jan 2016 - March 2016

- Build a website for the after-school services.
- Created media for advertising their services.

Interests

Gaming: Playing video games allows me to relax and clear my mind or if I want a challenge, I can improve my problem-solving skills and think outside the box playing a difficult game.

Programming: I enjoy developing small projects and constantly come up with new project ideas to create or ways to improve existing projects. I love to look up and research other developer's styles of coding to help mould my skills.

Language Learning: A lot of media and games I consume are from Japan so I set out a task to learn Japanese. It isn't a main hobby but when I have a bit of time on the side, I enjoy studying some kanji.

Drawing: when I am struggling with creative block, I find drawing helps to get my creative juices flowing.